Really now?
I'll take care of this, then!
I'll leave the rest to you...
Pythagoras!
Excuse me?!
Of course!
You don't get interesting
battle data like this every day!
I've got to draw up some blueprints!
So busy, so busy!
I'd even take help from a cat at this point!
Wonderful!
Excellent!
The seraphim's attack patterns
are developing as he grows!
Could this support my theory that experiences
are stored in one's hereditary elements?
Come on!
Really give it to 'em!
S-Shark!
This could be the solution to
the accelerated growth issue!
Heart rate over 90 BPM!
Green blood is flowing faster!
Show 'em what you're made of!
York the Greedy
The more I write...
the more my stomach growls!
There's no stoppin' these ideas!
I ain't got time to eat!
I need you to chow down for me, York!
Okay!
That's the ticket! My noggin
is soakin' up the nutrients!
I've got even more ideas!
Eat! Eat! York!
Another helping for you, Dr. York.
Nuh-uh, not enough!
Get me more!
Yes, doctor! Right away!
Yummy!
Her current BMI is over 600!
I don't want any more!
That's it, S-Shark!
The battle data keeps updating!
Oh no, not now...!
Ow, ow... I'm calling a temporary truce!
I can't miss this opportunity
to monitor his growth!
I gotta go to the bathroom,
but I can't waste any time!
Much better!
Digestion Punch!
That's it! Time to experiment!
Please bring me all materials
relating to devil fruits!
Deliver everything to Dr. Pythagoras!
Prep for Dr. Edison's experiment!
To simulation room 88!
Nap time.
That's Dr. York's fourth
snack, dump, nap cycle today!
Are you serious?!
That's enough, seraphim.
Stand down.
Edison, Lilith, Pythagoras!
I think you've had enough.
Oh, what a shame...
Consarn it!
Ouch!
Why's that scoundrel butting in?!
We were just getting to the good part!
Eureka!
Did that guy come to rescue us?
No way, he's just as shady
as the rest of them!
He's probably a colleague of Lilith's.
So this guy must be...
I am Dr. Vegapunk Shaka.
Shaka the Just
Another one?!
What's with you guys?!
You must be the Straw Hat Pirates.
We are! Now tell us what's
wrong with these shoes!
They're stuck to the floor!
Dom shoes can easily be controlled
by the magnets in the laboratory.
So resistance is futile, then.
We can't trust pirates.
There was also a female Vegapunk,
and another that was talking over the speakers...
Yeah...
I am Vegapunk as well.
I don't get it!
How many of you guys are there?!
Maybe I'm Vegapunk, too...
What?!
Like hell you are!
Does this island look like
the future to all of you?
Yeah, it's amazing!
It's not just any future!
There were those mechanical sea beasts!
Plus, the Vegaforce-01
and the island A.C. system, too!
It's a hell of a future!
And I've never seen a city like that...
I wanna snoop around
and see how everything works!
Don't be so cold!
Let's be pals, Vega!
Even my technology is still so far behind...
This island is from the past.
What?!
What do you mean "from the past"?!
What if I were to tell you...
that 900 years ago, there was
an advanced kingdom like Egghead...?
Would you believe me?
Nine hundred years ago?!
What are you talking about?!
It's real!
Look, Chopper!
It's not a holo-holo!
It's really there!
It's made of iron!
What is this?!
It's pretty beat-up.
Did it use to work?
That would require futuristic technology.
Isn't it too old?
I wanna ride it!
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's go, Chopper!